Dean Moroney

Multi-Disciplinary Graphic Designer

deanmcreative.com

+6421 0235 4235 | dean@deanmcreative.com

I am a 27 year old digital graphic designer and artist, currently based in Napier. I have a deep passion for all kinds of design, and love applying my skills to a range of discliplines. These include designing signage, posters, labels, packaging, brochures and wayfinding. I also have a range of skills in multimedia design such as websites, animation, video editing and projection mapping. My biggest projects to date have involved producing media all of these areas to form a cohesive outcome. In addition, I constantly work on my own projects - including having released two musical albums, and I am currently developing my own product: a neon-style lightbox, designed as an aesthetic feature for the home or office.

I have 7 years experience as both a freelance designer and working in an in-house design studio as part of EIT's ideaschool, and am very interested in extending my skillset and applying my skills to new areas.

Qualification

Bachelor of Visual Arts and Design (+ Top Design Student Award) EIT Hawke's Bay

2009 - 11

+ Self-Research and Self-Taught Skills

Employment

2012 - 14 ideaschool, EIT Hawke's Bay - In-House Graphic Design and Motion Design Tutor 2015 - 17 ideaschool, EIT Hawke's Bay - Design Consultation and Nightclass Tutor

+ Freelance Projects (Refer to Portfolio)

Skills

Extensive software knowledge and learning of new techniques and trends with ease

Deep understanding of branding, including preparation of brand guidelines and signage

Detailed knowledge of design principles and typography

Precision, attention to detail and efficiency

Software

Adobe Suite Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, InDesign, Premiere Pro, Muse

Cinema 4D 3D Animation

Blender Open-Source 3D Animation

Unity 5 3D Game Design and Development

Ableton Live Music and Sound Design

Microsoft Office Word, PowerPoint
Apple iWork Pages, Keynote

Google Drive, Docs, Slides, Search Console, G-Suite

Hobbies

Writing and Producing Music
Sketching and Concepting
Creation of abstract art using graphic design as a medium
Self-branding and constant reinvention